http://www.gajshield.com/gajshield-privacy-policy

GajShieldGajShield Privacy PolicyThis statement discloses the privacy practices for the site www.gajshield.com.GajShield uses reasonable efforts to protect your privacy as a consumer. This statement details for you the following:
What information we collect
How we use the information
With whom we share the information
We collect and store some or all of the following information about our users: name; email address; and billing information, such as address, phone number and credit card number. If you do not wish to have your credit card number stored, please contact Customer Support. We also receive and may store certain types of information whenever you interact with us. For example, like many Web sites, we use "cookies" and we obtain certain types of information when your Web browser accesses www.GajShield.com. More information on our use of "cookies" can be found below.
In order to tailor our subsequent communications to you and continuously improve our products and services (including registration), we may also ask you to provide us with information regarding your personal or professional interests, experience with our products, and more detailed contact preferences. Customers and visitors always have the option of choosing not to provide us with this information.
Web Applications
We may also employ certain applications, such as the various components of Security Center, to retrieve information about your computer system to assist us in the provision of services that you have chosen to subscribe to or use. This information is essential to enable us to provide you with quality service, and for that reason there is no opt-out available for this information collection.
Use of Data
GajShield uses your information to better understand your needs and provide you with better service. Specifically, we use your information to help you complete a transaction, including fulfillment of orders and promotional offers, to communicate back to you, to update you on service and benefits, to personalize our Web sites for you, and to manage and renew your subscription(s). Credit card numbers are used only for payment processing and fraud protection, and are not used for other purposes without your permission.
Use of Your Email Address
If you provide us with your email address when you register as a customer or make a purchase from us, we may occasionally send you email with recommendations or notices of new products, prices, and services. This email may include paid advertisements from third parties. At the time you register or make a purchase, you will be given the opportunity to opt into our out of this service. If you do not initially choose to opt out, you may still block future email of this type, simply by following the unsubscribe instructions that accompany all such communications.
Separately, we send service notifications via email to keep you informed about the status of your service orders or accounts and to provide updates and technical notices. These messages are essential to the maintenance of your subscription and the functionality of our services. Therefore there is no opt-out available for service notifications and these messages cannot be blocked.We follow industry standard practices for email marketing and customer contact, and we urge our business partners to do so as well.
Who We Share It With
GajShield will not sell, rent, or lease your personally information to others for commercial gain.
Links
Our site contains links to other Web sites. Please note that when you click on one of these links, you are 'clicking' to another Web site. As GajShield does not accept liability for misuse of any information by any Web site controller to which we may link, we encourage you to read the privacy statements of these linked sites, as their privacy policies may differ from ours.
Cookies
GajShield uses software tags called "cookies" to identify customers when they visit our site. Cookies are used to remember user preferences and maximize performance of our services. Additionally, cookies help us to identify returning users so that we don't ask them to enter their email and password with every visit. The information we collect with cookies is not sold, rented, or shared with any outside parties. We also ask that you fill in your first name and last name in a box so that our customer support services can identify and assist you in case of login problems. We cannot provide subscription services to users who do not give their consent to the data processing carried out through cookies or whose browsers are set to reject all cookies.
Log Files
GajShield maintains log files of the traffic that visits our site. We do not link any information gathered in these log files to personally identifying information. Log files are used to manage traffic loads and information technology requirements for providing reliable service. Information collected includes IP addresses and browser types.
Information Security
All information gathered on the site is stored and maintained in secure facilities that limit access to authorized personnel only. The GajShield Web sites are regularly tested for security breaches to ensure that all information collected is secure from unauthorized viewing.
Notification of Changes
If we make a change to our privacy policy, we will post a notice on our site so our users are aware of the change. If we make a significant change to the way we use, treat or disclose personal information, we will notify users by email.
Contacting Us
We would be happy to address any concerns you may have about our privacy practices and policies. If you have any questions or concerns, you can reach us through our “Contact Us” page.
Get In Touch With Us Subscribe to our NewsletterPlease fill the required field.PHA+SSBhbSBTdWJzY3JpYmVpbmcgeW91ciBOZXdzbGV0dGVyIGZyb20gbm93LiA8YnI+QWRkIG15IDxzdHJvbmc+RW1haWwgSUQgOjwvc3Ryb25nPiB7e2VtYWlsfX08L3A+Cg==Subscribe NowStay Connected
ABOUT US SUPPORT KNOWLEDGE BASE ALL PRODUCTS CAREERS Privacy PolicyDisclaimerWarranty Policy2020 © GajShield Infotech (I) Pvt. Ltd. All rights reserved.
